Guide to the Greek Life Office Records 1918-2015
Oregon State University Libraries, Special Collections and Archives Research Center
Greek Life Office Records
1918-2015
1988-2015
Oregon State University. Office of Greek Life.
RG 223
10.50 cubic feet, including 103 photographic prints 11 boxes, including 1 oversize box
3.13 Gbytes 711 files
Special Collections and Archives Research Center 121 The Valley Library Oregon State University Corvallis, OR, 97331-4501 Phone: 541-737-2075 Email: scarc@oregonstate.edu Web: http://scarc.library.oregonstate.edu/findingaids
The Greek Life Office Records document the administration of this office, which regulates and provides support services to the fraternity and sorority community at Oregon State University. These materials were primarily generated by the Greek Life Office and reflect administrative activities such as the development of training workshops/classes, the compilation of membership statistics, collaboration with law enforcement agencies in educational programming, and the evaluation of annual rush activities. The Greek Life Office was established in 1998. Access to the Judicial Sanction Files in Series 15 is restricted due to the presence of confidential information. All requests for access to these materials should be directed to the University Archivist.
Historical Note:
The beginnings of Greek letter social organizations at Oregon State University date back to the formation of the Gamma Delta Phi fraternity in 1905. This group was organized at a local level as more of a club than a recognized chapter and soon inspired the establishment of other local greek letter organizations such as Kappa Sigma Nu (1906), Phi Delta Sigma (1914), and Gamma Upsilon (1913). In 1915, two fraternities, Alpha Chi Omega and Sigma Alpha Epsilon, became the first at Oregon State Univerity to receive official recognition as chapters of national fraternal organizations. After these chapters set the groundwork for establishing a Greek presence at Oregon State University, the fraternity and sorority community grew rapidly. This growth is reflected in the 1925 Beaver Yearbook which lists 50 established Greek chapters (34 fraternities and 16 sororities) on campus that year.
The Panhellenic and Interfraternity Councils were established in 1917 and 1927, respectively, to serve as the student governing bodies of the Oregon State University Greek community. All sororities and fraternities have representation on the councils, which have the authority to offer direct recommendations to the university and regulate areas not covered by institutional policies.
Membership in the Greek community at Oregon State University has fluctuated over time owing to a number of factors. Chief among them has been the competition posed by the post-World War II growth in campus residence halls and a changing college culture emergent in the 1960s activist movements.
Until 1970, university administration of the Oregon State University Greek community resided in the hands of the Dean of Women and the Dean of Men. With the closure of these gender based student administrative offices, Oregon State University placed the management of fraternities and sororities under a single office, the Assistant Dean of Students. In 1998, an administrative reorganization that eliminated the Assistant Dean of Students position resulted in the establishment of a new office, the Greek Life Office. With the formation of this office, Oregon State University for the first time had an administrator devoted solely to the management of the Greek community. The Greek Life Office, in turn, served as one of the six "functional areas" managed by the Office of Student Leadership and Involvement. In 2015, the office was renamed the Center for Fraternity and Sorority Life.
Greek Life Coordinators have been Clay Torset (1998-2000), Robert Kerr (2000-2015), and Leslie Schacht-Drey (2015-present).
Oregon State University--Student housing.; Oregon State University--Students.; Oregon State University. Office of Greek Life.
Born digital.; Photographic prints.; Posters.
College students--Alcohol use--Oregon--Corvallis.; College students--Oregon--Corvallis--Social life and customs.; College students--Oregon--Corvallis.; Greek letter societies--Oregon--Corvallis.; Minority college students--Oregon--Corvallis.; Student activities--Oregon--Corvallis.
Clubs and Societies; Colleges and Universities; Multiculturalism; Performing Arts; Student Life; Corvallis; Oregon; Artifacts; Electronic Records; Moving Images; Photographs
These materials were transferred to the Special Collections and Archives Research Center between 2004 and 2017.
Access to Judicial Sanction Files in Series 15 is restricted due to the presence of confidential information. All requests for access to these materials should be directed to the University Archivist. All other materials in this collection are open for research.
Other collections documenting the administration of the Greek community at OSU prior to the formation of the Greek Life Office in 1998 include: the Dean of Women Records (RG 57), the Dean of Men Records (RG 134), and the Dean of Students Office Records (RG 285). Documentation of the Greek Life Office can also be found in the collection of its administrative parent, the Office of Student Leadership and Involvement Records (RG 232).
Records of the student management of Greek life through the governing bodies of the Interfraternity Council and the Panhellenic Council also represented in the collections of SCARC.
Images of Greek activity and chapter houses are featured in a number of photographic collections including: Harriet's Photographic Collection, the Fraternities and Sororities Photograph Collection (P 034), the Gamma Phi Beta Sorority Photograph Collection (P 277), Smith-Western Company Photographs of OSC (P 164), and the Gwil Evans Photograph Collection (P 082).
Film and video footage of two Greek events at OSU are available streaming online, these are the 1999 performance of the annual Interfraternity Council (IFC) Sing concert and a feature about the 1963 sorority rush.
The Greek Life Office Records consists of 15 series: 1. Correspondence, 1949-2013; 2. Reports, 1961-2011; 3. Committees, 1954-2011; 4. Chapter Files, 1918-2015; 5. Statistics, 1924-2009; 6. Newspaper Clippings, 1970-2015; 7. Handbooks, 1968-2011; 8. Publications, 1971-2015; 9.Surveys, 1970-2009; 10. Speeches and Presentations, 2000-2015; 11. Event Registration Lists, 1999-2007; 12. Subject Files, 1968-2011; 13. Photographs, 1945-2013; 14. Artifacts, 1976-1985; and 15. Judicial Sanction Files, 1996-2008.
The Greek Life Office Records document the administration of this office, which regulates and provides support services to fraternity and sorority chapters at Oregon State University. These records were generated and assembled by the Greek Life office and include: annual review forms, articles of incorporation, artifacts, brochures, bylaws, constitutions, correspondence, digital files, handbooks, meeting minutes, newsletters, newspaper clippings, photographs, reports, statistics, and survey materials.
These records primarily reflect administrative activities by the Greek Life Office that document interaction with chapter leadership, compilation of Greek membership statistics, the evaluation of annual rush activities, the development of training workshops/classes, collaboration with law enforcement in educational programming, policy clarification, response to student conduct issues, and the survey of students regarding their perceptions of the Greek community.
Materials relating to particular Oregon State University fraternity and sorority chapters can be found in Series 4, which is made up of a combination of annual review forms, articles of incorporation, bylaws, colonization proposals, constitutions, correspondence, flyers, newsletters, newspaper clippings, and policy reports.
Activities organized by the Greek community are reflected in event registration lists, newspaper clippings, photographs, and chapter files.
Born digital materials in this collection are in a variety of formats: Word documents, Excel Spreadsheets, and PowerPoint presentations. They are available for viewing in the Reading Room.
- Correspondence, 1949-2013; Series 1
  Series 1 is made up of correspondence, letters, and memoranda reflecting interaction between the Greek Life Office and fraternity/sorority chapter presidents, other OSU departments, law enforcement agencies, alumni organizations, and Greek life administrators at other universities. Topics covered in this series include: policy clarification, risk management policies, Greek leadership training classes, and educational programming geared toward traditions such as Shasta Weekend.
  - Accreditation, 2004-2006 (Box-folder 1.1)
  - Advanced Tuition Deposit Lists, 1997-2004 (Box-folder 1.2)
  - Alcohol Policies, 1975-2006 (Box-folder 1.3)
  - Alcohol Status of Chapters, 2004-2007 (Box-folder 1.4)
  - Alumni Volunteer Academy, 2009 (Box-folder 1.5)
  - Annual Registration and Recognition Process, 2001-2007 (Box-folder 1.6)
  - Assessment, 2006-2008 (Box-folder 1.7)
  - Beaver Community Fair, 2006 (Box-folder 1.8)
  - Codes to Student Learner Activities, 2006-2008 (Box-folder 1.9)
  - Collaborative Housing/Greek Life Recruitment Mailer, 2002 (Box-folder 1.10)
  - Compilation of Statistics, 1965-2003 (Box-folder 1.11)
  - Compliance, 2000-2004 (Box-folder 1.12)
  - Constitution and Bylaw Submission by Chapters, 2002-2006 (Box-folder 1.13)
  - Corvallis Police Department, 1995-2003 (Box-folder 1.14)
  - Cultural Diversity Programming For the Greek Community, 1988-1992 (Box-folder 1.15)
  - Dean of Women, 1949-1963 (Box-folder 1.16)
  - Faculty Associates, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 1.17)
  - Fire Safety Processes, 1975-1977; 2005-2008 (Box-folder 1.18)
  - Firearms Policies, 2006-2007 (Box-folder 1.19)
  - Five Star Living Group Standards Evaluation Program, 1995-1998 (Box-folder 1.20)
  - Focus Group on the "College Experience" Plan, 2004 (Box-folder 1.21)
  - General, 1980-2013 (Box-folder 1.22)
  - Greek Adviser Position, 1989-1996 (Box-folder 1.23)
  - Greek Community Demographic Analysis, 2003 (Box-folder 1.24)
  - Greek Community Master Calendar, 1999-2004 (Box-folder 1.25)
  - Greek Congress, 2001 (Box-folder 1.26)
  - Greek Leadership Classes, 1980-2008 (Box-folder 1.27-1.29)
    Courses specifically oriented toward Greek chapter presidents and members of the IFC/Panhellenic Councils. The classes featured are "Leadership Training" (HIED 406P) and "Living Group Presidents Class" (CSSA 406), and "Creating Positive Change" (AHE 499).
  - Greek Leadership Programs/Retreats, 2000-2008 (Box-folder 1.30)
  - Greek Matriculation Ceremony, 2000-2008 (Box-folder 1.31)
  - Ideas For Community and Diversity Campus Initiative Plan, 2004 (Box-folder 1.32)
  - International Student Sorority/Fraternity Cultural Exchange Program, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 1.33)
  - Intramural Sports Fraternity Eligibility Guidelines, 2006 (Box-folder 1.34)
  - Membership Selection Policies and Discrimination Cases, 1960-1979 (Box-folder 1.35)
  - National Panhellenic Conference, 1969-1976 (Box-folder 1.36)
  - National Panhellenic Conference, 1971-1999 (Box-folder 2.1-2.2)
  - Office Renovation, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 2.3)
  - OSU College Panhellenic NPC Summit, 2006 (Box-folder 2.4)
  - Pledge Education Program, 1964-1993 (Box-folder 2.5)
  - Policies and Procedures-General, 1981-1999 (Box-folder 2.6)
  - Portland Panhellenic Association, 1979 (Box-folder 2.7)
  - Records Archiving and Privacy Guidelines, 2003-2006 (Box-folder 2.8)
  - Recruitment, 1998-2003 (Box-folder 2.9)
  - Risk Management Policies, 2006-2007 (Box-folder 2.10-2.11)
  - Scholarships, 2001-2004 (Box-folder 2.12)
  - Shasta Weekend Incidents and Risk Management, 1985-2006 (Box-folder 2.13-2.15)
  - Sorority Rushing and Semester Calendar Change, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 2.16)
  - Statement of the Relationship Between OSU and the Greek System, 1963-2002 (Box-folder 2.17)
  - Student Activities Committee Approval Process For Recognition, 2008 (Box-folder 2.18)
  - Student Conduct and Mediation Database, 2002 (Box-folder 2.19)
  - Student Involvement Office Retreat, 2002 (Box-folder 2.20)
  - Summer Advising and Registration Program (START), 2002-2005 (Box-folder 2.21)
  - Title IX and Fraternal Organizations, 1974 (Box-folder 2.22)
  - Wall of Values/Creeds/Mission Statements, 2000-2005 (Box-folder 2.23)
  - Website Management, 2001-2008 (Box-folder 2.24-2.25)
- Reports, 1961-2011; Series 2
  Series 2 is made up of reports issued by the Office of Greek Life, the Office of the Dean of Students, and the Student Affairs Task Force on Greek Life.
  - All-Greek Circle of Excellence, 2011 (Box-folder 2.26)
  - Annual Reports, 1969-2007 (Box-folder 2.27)
  - Campus Health Action on Tobacco Study, 2003 (Box-folder 2.28)
  - Interfraternal Summit Discussion Summary, 2011 (Box-folder 2.29)
  - OSI Greek Transition Analysis, 2007 (Box-folder 2.30)
  - OSU 2007 Interfraternity and Panhellenic Council's Proposal, 2003 (Box-folder 2.31)
  - Potential Liability Regarding Shasta, 2002 (Box-folder 2.32)
  - Recruitment Reports and Guides, 1998-2008 (Box-folder 2.33)
  - Report to Vice Provost for Student Affairs and Student Affairs Division-Reorganization Assessment, 2005 (Box-folder 2.34)
  - Student Affairs Task Force on Greek Life-Report and Recommendations, 1998 (Box-folder 2.35)
  - Study of the Present Sorority Situation, 1961 (Box-folder 2.36)
- Committees, 1954-2011; Series 3
  Series 3 reflects the work of various OSU committees, the Panhellenic Council, and the Interfraternity Council. In addition to meeting minutes, this series includes correspondence, bylaws, newspaper clippings, notes, and reports.
  - Alumni Interfraternity Council, 1954-1967 (Box-folder 3.1)
  - Fraternity/Sorority Chapter Advisers, 1981; 1995 (Box-folder 3.2)
  - Greek Advisory Committee, 1973-1999 (Box-folder 3.3)
  - Greek Life Marketing Task Force, 2004-2009 (Box-folder 3.4)
  - Greek Life Task Force, 2000-2003 (Box-folder 3.5)
  - Greek Life Team, 2000-2003 (Box-folder 3.6)
  - Interfraternity Council, 1986-2011 (Box-folder 3.7)
  - National Interfraternity Council (NIC) Academic Committee, 2006 (Box-folder 3.8)
  - OSU Alcohol Work Group, 2004-2009 (Box-folder 3.9)
  - Panhellenic Council, 1967-2011 (Box-folder 3.10)
  - Panhellenic Council, 2005-2011
    This folder is made up of 692 born digital files generated by the Panhellenic Council, the Panhellenic Advisory Board, and the Corvallis Area Alumnae Panhellenic (CAAP). In addition to meeting minutes and agendas, these files contain membership statistics, bylaws, constitutions, recruitment schedule information, and weekly bulletins. These files are available for viewing in the Reading Room.
  - Student Affairs Task Force on Greek Life, 1997-2000 (Box-folder 3.11)
  - Student Leadership Initiative Group, 2002-2005 (Box-folder 3.12)
- Chapter Files, 1918-2015; Series 4
  Series 4 documents fraternity and sorority chapters and is primarily organized alphabetically by chapter. This series contains annual review forms, articles of incorporation, bylaws, charter records, constitutions, correspondence, event programs, newsletters, newspaper clippings, recolonization proposals, reports, and risk management plans.
  - Articles of Incorporation for Various Chapters, 1918-1974 (Box-folder 10.1)
  - Chapter Information in Various Lists, 1983-2012 (Box-folder 3.13)
  - Acacia Fraternity, 1989-2003 (Box-folder 3.14)
  - Alpha Chi Omega, 1983-2012 (Box-folder 3.15)
  - Alpha Delta Pi, 1981-2011 (Box-folder 3.16-3.17)
    2 folders.
  - Alpha Gamma Delta, 1987-2015 (Box-folder 3.18)
  - Alpha Gamma Rho, 1986-2007 (Box-folder 3.19)
  - Alpha Kappa Alpha, 1989-2006 (Box-folder 3.20)
  - Alpha Kappa Lambda, 1990-1994 (Box-folder 3.21)
  - Alpha Omicron Pi, 2011-2014 (Box-folder 3.22)
  - Alpha Phi, 1981-2007 (Box-folder 3.23)
  - Alpha Phi Alpha, 1995-1997 (Box-folder 3.24)
  - Alpha Sigma Phi, 1983-2010 (Box-folder 3.25)
  - Alpha Tau Omega, 1991-2007 (Box-folder 3.26)
  - Alpha Xi Delta, 1978-2005 (Box-folder 3.27)
  - Beta Theta Pi, 1981-2002 (Box-folder 3.28)
  - Chi Omega, 1981-2013 (Box-folder 3.29)
  - Chi Phi, 1979-2010 (Box-folder 4.1)
  - Delta Chi, 1981-2007 (Box-folder 4.2)
  - Delta Delta Delta, 1985-2003 (Box-folder 4.3)
  - Delta Gamma, 1981-2010 (Box-folder 4.4)
  - Delta Phi Omega, 2005-2007 (Box-folder 4.5)
  - Delta Sigma Phi, 1999-2008 (Box-folder 4.6-4.7)
  - Delta Sigma Theta, 2006-2013 (Box-folder 4.8)
  - Delta Tau Delta, 1983-2001 (Box-folder 4.9)
  - Delta Upsilon, 1979-2013 (Box-folder 4.10)
  - Delta Xi Phi, 2005 (Box-folder 4.11)
  - Gamma Alpha Omega, 2000-2010 (Box-folder 4.12)
  - Gamma Phi Beta, 1981-2002 (Box-folder 4.13)
  - Gamma Sigma Alpha, 1996-2008 (Box-folder 4.14)
  - Kappa Alpha Psi, 1977-2003 (Box-folder 4.15)
  - Kappa Alpha Theta, 1965-2013 (Box-folder 4.16)
  - Kappa Delta, 1987-2015 (Box-folder 4.17)
  - Kappa Delta Chi, 2011-2012 (Box-folder 4.18)
  - Kappa Delta Rho, 1927-2012 (Box-folder 4.19)
  - Kappa Kappa Gamma, 1981-2008 (Box-folder 4.20)
  - Kappa Sigma, 1963-2013 (Box-folder 4.21)
  - Lambda Chi Alpha, 1981-2010 (Box-folder 4.22-4.23)
  - Lambda Theta Alpha, 2007 (Box-folder 4.24)
  - Lambda Theta Phi, 2008 (Box-folder 4.25)
  - Omega Delta Phi, 1998-2010 (Box-folder 4.26)
  - Phi Delta Theta, 1981-2012 (Box-folder 4.27)
  - Phi Gamma Delta, 1985-2013 (Box-folder 4.28)
  - Phi Gamma Delta PNW Joint Section Convention, 2004 (Box-folder 4.29)
  - Phi Kappa Psi, 1981-2008 (Box-folder 5.1)
  - Phi Kappa Sigma, 1983 (Box-folder 5.2)
  - Phi Kappa Tau, 1996-2001 (Box-folder 5.3-5.4)
  - Phi Kappa Theta, 1965 (Box-folder 5.5)
  - Phi Sigma Kappa, 1987-2003 (Box-folder 5.6)
  - Phi Sigma Rho, 2003-2006 (Box-folder 5.7)
  - Pi Beta Phi, 1981-2006 (Box-folder 5.8)
  - Pi Kappa Alpha, 1981-2006 (Box-folder 5.9)
  - Pi Kappa Phi, 1986-2015 (Box-folder 5.10)
  - Pi Kappa Phi - Chartering Document, 2003; 5.1 (Box-item 5.1)
    Folder consists of 1 bound volume.
  - Sigma Alpha, 1991-2004 (Box-folder 5.11)
  - Sigma Alpha Epsilon, 1986-2011 (Box-folder 5.12)
  - Sigma Beta Rho, undated (Box-folder 5.13)
  - Sigma Chi, 1984-2007 (Box-folder 5.14)
  - Sigma Delta Omega, 2006-2013 (Box-folder 5.15)
  - Sigma Kappa, 1985-2007 (Box-folder 5.16)
  - Sigma Lambda Delta, 2002-2006 (Box-folder 5.17)
  - Sigma Nu, 1986-2006 (Box-folder 5.18)
  - Sigma Phi Epsilon, 1983-2007 (Box-folder 5.19)
  - Sigma Pi, 1981-2004 (Box-folder 5.20)
  - Tau Kappa Epsilon, 1977-2008 (Box-folder 5.21)
  - Theta Chi, 1986-2006 (Box-folder 5.22)
  - Triangle Fraternity, 2008 (Box-folder 5.23)
  - Order of Omega, 1976-2006 (Box-folder 5.24)
  - Chapter Files, 2002-2006
    This folder is made up of 13 born digital files that contain bylaws, constitutions, risk management plans, and policy guides from various fraternity and sorority chapters. These files are available for viewing in the Reading Room.
- Statistics, 1924-2009; Series 5
  Series 5 is comprised of statistical information reflecting various aspects of the OSU Greek community: chapter grade point averages membership expenses, members by major, members by class, canceled contracts, members living outside the house, and students involved in rush/pledge activities.
  - Demographic Data, 1929-2007 (Box-folder 6.1-6.5)
    5 folders.
  - Demographic Data, 1970-1979 (Box-folder 10.2)
  - Demographic Survey Forms, 1973-1996 (Box-folder 6.6)
  - Expense and Cost Information, 1955-2000 (Box-folder 10.3)
  - Minorities in the Greek System, 1990-2003 (Box-folder 6.7)
    Some of the data is featured in Greek Leadership class research papers.
  - Rush and Pledge Activity Data, 1953-2000 (Box-folder 6.8-6.11)
    4 folders.
  - Rush and Pledge Activity Data, 1962-1988 (Box-folder 10.4)
  - Scholarship Reporting By Chapter, 1975-2008 (Box-folder 6.12-6.14)
    3 folders.
  - Scholarship Reporting By Year, 1924-2009 (Box-folder 6.15-6.20)
- Newspaper Clippings, 1970-2015; Series 6
  Series 6 is made up of newspaper articles featuring stories about OSU fraternities and sororities and were featured primarily in the The Daily Barometer, The Corvallis Gazette-Times, and The Oregonian.
  - General, 1970-1992 (Box-folder 6.21)
  - General, 1993-2015 (Box-folder 6.22)
  - General, 2007 (Box-folder 10.5)
  - Greek Communities at Other Universities, 1973-2002 (Box-folder 6.23)
  - Greek Enrollment Trends, 1977-2007 (Box-folder 6.24)
  - Interfraternity Council (IFC) Sing, 1983-2014 (Box-folder 6.25)
  - Shasta Weekend, 2001-2008 (Box-folder 6.26)
- Handbooks, 1968-2012; Series 7
  Series 7 consists of handbooks, manuals, and guides generated by the Greek Life Office and other OSU departments. These materials were designed to orient students to the rush/pledge process, the regulations governing chapter leadership, the guidelines for planning events within the Greek community, and engagement with the Corvallis Police Department through the Greek liaison program.
  - Associate Member/Pledge Education Guides, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 6.27)
  - Association of Fraternity Advisors (AFA) Membership Handbook, 2008 (Box-folder 6.28)
  - Big Brother Manual, undated (Box-folder 6.29)
    Kappa Sigma
  - Center For Fraternity and Sorority Life Guide, 2011 (Box-folder 6.30)
  - Chapter President's Manual, 2002 (Box-folder 7.1)
  - Collegiate Student Services Administration (CSSA) GTA Supervisor Guide, 2000 (Box-folder 7.2)
  - Corvallis Police Department Greek Liaison Program Manual, 2009 (Box-folder 7.3)
  - Creating Positive Change: A Facilitator's Guide to Training In The Greek Community, undated (Box-folder 7.4)
  - Document and Process Deadlines: Greek Community @ OSU, 2007 (Box-folder 7.5)
  - Event Registration Manual, 2008 (Box-folder 7.6)
  - Greek Community Recruitment Information, 2008 (Box-folder 7.7)
  - Greek Leadership Manuals, 2000-2004 (Box-folder 7.8)
  - Greek Scholarship Chair Manual, 2003 (Box-folder 7.9)
  - Housemother Manual, 1968 (Box-folder 7.10)
  - Judicious Leadership for Sororities: Some Helpful Hints on Judicial Matters, undated (Box-folder 7.11)
  - Leadership Orientation Packet, 2007 (Box-folder 7.12)
  - National Panhellenic Conference Manual of Information, 1999 (Box-folder 7.13)
  - OSU Fraternity Scholarship Program, 1979 (Box-folder 7.14)
  - OSU Greek Community Resident Advisor Reference Manual, 2009 (Box-folder 7.15)
  - Presidential Tips To Success, 2008 (Box-folder 7.16)
  - Retreat Planning Handbook, undated (Box-folder 7.17)
  - Rush and Recruitment Handbooks, 1998-2012 (Box-folder 7.18)
  - Safe Space Training, 2004 (Box-folder 7.19)
  - Student Activities Committee Handbook, 2008 (Box-folder 7.20)
  - Student Involvement GTA Manual, 2001 (Box-folder 7.21)
  - Student Life Policy and Regulations, 1993 (Box-folder 7.22)
  - Things You Wanted To Know About the Office of Greek Life But Never Asked, 2004 (Box-folder 7.23)
- Publications, 1971-2015; Series 8
  Series 8 consists of publications produced and collected by the Office of Greek Life that include newsletters, brochures, research bulletins, and journal articles.
  - Articles and Book Chapters, 2001-2012 (Box-folder 7.24)
    These published articles and chapters were written by Greek Life Director Robert Kerr.
  - Descriptive Research Bulletins, 1971-1982 (Box-folder 7.25)
    The research focuses on the first term academic achievement and graduation rates of fraternity members. These bulletins were published as part of a series issued by the OSU Office of the Dean of Students and the Counseling and Testing Center.
  - Event Programs and Flyers, 2004-2015 (Box-folder 7.26)
    Includes programs for Greek Centennial celebration events in 2015.
  - Handouts, 1986-2008 (Box-folder 7.27)
  - Informational Brochures, 1992-2011 (Box-folder 7.28)
  - Newsletters, 1977-2010 (Box-folder 7.29-7.32)